# Mário Antônio A. Rodeghiero

FRONT END · DEVELOPER

88034-102, Rod. Amaro Antônio Vieira 2259 Apt. 404, Florianópolis - SC, Brazil

□ (+55) 99691-2866 | ■ mario.rodeghiero@gmail.com | ★ www.mrodeghiero.com | 回 mariorodeghiero | □ mariorodeghiero

## Summary\_

After a solid career of 10 years in the telecommunications area, I decided to change the area and look for new challenges. My free time to study development, contribute to Open Source projects and improve my English. Graduate student in Data science and Big Data Analytics and in parallel I continue my studies focused on Front End, I have as main programming language "Javascript" but I also have knowledge of Python and I love ReactJS. I keep my personal codes and projects on Github and I have also developed my blog to put my learning into practice by publishing articles on development. I am also the creator of "Vue Theme", theme with more than 43600 Installs in the Visual Studio Code editor.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Claro S/A Florianópolis - Brazil

DATACENTER ANALYST II

Apr 2013 - Jun 2017

• Responsible for implementing and managing the Datacenter infrastructure, installing, configuring, monitoring and performing preventive and corrective maintenance on large equipment in high-availability environments and mission critical as servers (Oracle Solaris) DHCP, DNS, TFTP, LDAP, routers (Cisco and Huawei), Switches (Cisco) and CMTS (Cisco, Arris, House System and Motorola), responsible for the generation and distribution of DOCSIS technology services (broadband Internet, VOIP and video On Demand) through the HFC network, for more than 170,000 customers in the cities of Florianópolis, São José and Palhoça. Main activities also include the management of LAN and WAN networks (IPv4, IPv6, and NAT) routing, BGP, IS-IS and OSPF, and traffic Balancing control, administration of links, monitoring, troubleshooting and network documentation, assist in developing and maintaining internal systems, through markup languages, programming and database, such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and level 2 support to the operations of course Brazil (Net, Embratel) throughout the State of Santa Catarina, helping, guiding and planning demands for Datacenter teams to the cities of Balneário Camboriú, Blumenau, Brusque, Chapecó, Criciúma, Itajaí, Itapema, Joinville and Navegantes.

Claro S/A Florianópolis - Brazil

TECHNICIAN III

Aug 2012 to Apr 2013

NET S/A Florianópolis - Brazil

TECHNICIAN II

Jun 2010 - Jul 2012

**RCtel Solution in Telecommunications** 

Florianópolis - Brazil

Support Analyst Aug 2008 - May 2010

#### Education\_

University Estácio de Sá

Florianópolis, Brazil

GRADUATE STUDIES DATA SCIENCE AND BIG DATA ANALYTICS

Dec. 2018 - PRESENT

University Estácio de Sá

Florianópolis, Brazil

TECHNICIAN'S LICENSE COMPUTER NETWORKS

Dec. 2016

### Technical skills

ReactJS, Javascript, ES6, Python, HTML, CSS, SASS (Preprocessor), styled-components, ElectronJS, Css Frameworks(Bootstrap), Git e Github, Webpack, Gulp and Programming logic.

## Languages \_\_\_\_

Portuguese (fluent), English (intermediate)